{
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Java object oriented programming concepts is/are",
      "choices": ["Encapsulation", "Inheritance", "polymorphism", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Java does not support _______________?",
      "choices": ["Inheritance", "Multiple inheritance for classes", "multiple inheritance of interfaces", "compile time polymorphism"],
      "answer": "Multiple inheritance for classes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Runtime polymorphism feature in java is",
      "choices": ["method overriding", "method overloading", "constructor overloading", "operator overloading"],
      "answer": "method overriding"
    },
    {
      "question": "Encapsulation concept in java is",
      "choices": ["Hiding complexity", "method hiding", "Hiding constructor", "None"],
      "answer": "Hiding complexity"
    },
    {
      "question": "Following concept can be used for encapsulation in java programs",
      "choices": ["Wrapping data fields with methods", "Hiding data and internal methods using access modifiers in a class", "Using Interfaces", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
      "question": "Exposing only necessary information to clients ( main programs, classes) is known as",
      "choices": ["Abstraction", "Encapsulation", "Data hiding", "Hiding complexity"],
      "answer": "Abstraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hiding the complexity in program is known as",
      "choices": ["Abstraction", "Encapsulation", "Data hiding", "Composition"],
      "answer": "Encapsulation"
    },
    {
      "question": "For Cat and Animal class, correct way of inheritance in java is",
      "choices": ["class Cat extends Animal", "class Animal extends Cat", "Both are correct way", "None is correct way"],
      "answer": "class Cat extends Animal"
    },
    {
      "question": "In a class, encapsulating an object of another class is called",
      "choices": ["Composition", "Inheritance", "Encapsulation", "None"],
      "answer": "Composition"
    },
    {
      "question": "Polymorphism types in Java is/are",
      "choices": ["Compile time", "Run time", "Both", "None"],
      "answer": "Both"
    }
  ]
}